I've been seeing <symptom CUI="C0085635">flashing lights</symptom> now for about a week, it only happens when I touch my eye.
Three weeks ago his <symptom CUI="C0005858">eye started to bleed</symptom>.
Just moments ago, I experienced sudden <symptom CUI="C2126074">blurred vision</symptom> in my left eye.
About a week ago I started experiencing <symptom CUI="C0013456">ear aches</symptom> that would almost take me to my knee's.
I have <symptom CUI="C0007859" NO="YES">no pains in my neck</symptom>.
My son aged 4 years is known to have complete <symptom CUI="C1879328">loss of vision </symptom>in his left eye due to poor optic nerve.
Since 3 days I can <symptom CUI="C0920171">feel something in my left eye</symptom>.
When I press the <symptom CUI="C0151827">eye ball i can feel the pain</symptom>.
My <symptom CUI="C0314719">eyes recently have been extremely dry</symptom> and <symptom CUI="C0085636">sensitive to light</symptom>.
About five days ago I woke up with a <symptom CUI="C0235267">red left eye</symptom> and <symptom CUI="C0560024">swollen eyelids</symptom>.
I've also been having <symptom CUI="C2203736">mucosy discharge from eye </symptom>since then that has matted my eyelids together in the morning.
I woke up two days ago with <symptom CUI="C0235267">redness in my right eye</symptom>.
I am a 20 year old male experiencing <symptom CUI="C0030197">eye pain</symptom> and occasional <symptom CUI="C0018681">headaches</symptom>. 
My name is Juli and I have been suffering from <symptom CUI="C0314719">dry eyes for a long time</symptom>.
It began when i started to have <symptom CUI="C0012833">dizziness</symptom> and <symptom CUI="C0018681">headache</symptom> 3 years ago.
My left <symptom CUI="C3257803">eye waters</symptom> almost continuously.
I believe the water is causing my <symptom CUI="C0344232">vision to be blurry</symptom>.
My nose is started getting cold and my left <symptom CUI="C2054488">teeth were very sensitive to cold</symptom>.
I have had a <symptom CUI="C0850674">twitch in my eye</symptom> for three months now.
I also have a constant <symptom CUI="C0151827">pressure behind my eye</symptom> as well as <symptom CUI="C0151827">pain</symptom> when i squeeze my eyes.
Last night I had a sudden and intense <symptom CUI="C0151827">pain behind my left eye</symptom>.
It burned somewhat and my <symptom CUI="C3257803">eye watered</symptom> quite a bit but then as sudden as it had came, it went away.
My symptoms now are: severly <symptom CUI="C0314719">dry eyes </symptom>in the morning, <symptom CUI="C0085636">terrible light sensitivity</symptom>.
I <symptom CUI="C0233407">feel disoriented </symptom>and my <symptom CUI="C0004095">eyes feel very strained, tired and heavy</symptom> after 2 hours of continuous use on one task.
I occasionally feel <symptom CUI="C0151827">sharp pain in the back of my eye</symptom> and I have <symptom CUI="C0018681">headaches in the back of my head and temples</symptom>.
I've had <symptom CUI="C0560024">swelling on my upper eyelid of my left eye</symptom>, and there's some <symptom CUI="C0151827">pain on the left side of my eye </symptom>as well.
About four days ago I started having <symptom CUI="C0151827">pain in one of my eyes</symptom>.
Over the last few months I have started to notice that <symptom CUI="C0235267">my left eye becomes red and bloodshot </symptom>after prolong use of the computer.
On cold windy days my left <symptom CUI="C3257803">eye always start to tear up</symptom>.
Now I get a <symptom CUI="C0151827">throbbing pain in the corner of my eye </symptom>up my bridge of my nose and forehead, I have a <symptom CUI="C0424755">fever </symptom>and real bad <symptom CUI="C0018681">headaches</symptom>.
I also have a mucus laden <symptom CUI="C0010200">cough</symptom>, <symptom CUI="C0027424">runny nose</symptom>.
My 5 year old son woke up with <symptom CUI="C0235267">redness </symptom>.
I have something wrong with my <symptom CUI="C0560024">top left eyelid it is swollen</symptom>.
I have noticed a <symptom CUI="C2126956">white spot in my vision </symptom>lately.
I'm 17, and for the past two years I've noticed that i have been getting a lot of <symptom CUI="C2203736">mucous in my eyes</symptom>.
I recently experienced sudden <symptom CUI="C0012569">temporary double vision</symptom>.
Both eyes seem to have small cuts at the corners and they are both <symptom CUI="C0235267">red</symptom>.
For the past few days, <symptom CUI="C3257803">my left eye has been "tearing"</symptom>.
When I lay in bed in the morning <symptom CUI="C0344232">my eyesight is blurry</symptom>.
I have noticed that for a whole month now <symptom CUI="C0850674">my left eye has twitched</symptom> non stop.
My <symptom CUI="C0241681">vision is distorted</symptom>.
I've had almost constant <symptom CUI="C0151827">pain in my eyes especially my right eye</symptom>.
My <symptom CUI="C2012639">left eye has a small lump </symptom>too in the same spot.
My <symptom CUI="C3257803">eyes get teary </symptom>so easily when I start to laugh, even a soft laugh.
My <symptom CUI="C0151827">eyes hurt</symptom> all of the time.
I have been having <symptom CUI="C0151827">right eye pain in the corner of the eye</symptom>.
The next morning there was <symptom CUI="C0235267">redness in the white part of eye</symptom> and it was obvious that it was hit.
I have full <symptom CUI="C0314719">dry eye</symptom> on both eyes.
