She is affected with <symptom CUI="C0027498">vomiting</symptom> happening all the day.
It feels like ther is <symptom CUI="C0426484">something stuck in my throat</symptom> a ways down on the right side.
I noticed a really bad <symptom CUI="C0000737">abdominal ache</symptom> after drinking orange juice at first.
I was having bouts of <symptom CUI="C0011991">diarrhea</symptom> and <symptom CUI="C0238551">pain on my lower left quadrant</symptom>.
my son-in-law has a problem with <symptom CUI="C0011991">diarrhea</symptom> after eating anything.
I had severe <symptom CUI="C2004489">acid reflux</symptom> for 7 yrs with no relief no matter what i took, prescription, otc ..nothing!
Hi, during the past week I've had <symptom CUI="C0027497">nausea</symptom> and <symptom CUI="C0028643">numbness most prevalent in the right side of my tongue</symptom>.
Within the past 6 months, I have been noticing a strange <symptom CUI="C0008031">chest pain</symptom> that has me concerned.
At varying distances during many of my runs, I will get a short, but sharp <symptom CUI="C0008031">chest pain right in the middle of my chest</symptom>.
I have been having <symptom CUI="C0027497">nausea</symptom>, at irregular times, sometimes lasting several hours.
I have chronic <symptom CUI="C0027497">nausea</symptom>.
Everytime I would eat I would become really <symptom CUI="C0027497">nauseas</symptom>.
On Tuesday I woke up at 4a.m with severe constant <symptom CUI="C0000737">abdominal pains in the centre of my stomach</symptom>.
For the past few months I have been having nearly constant <symptom CUI="C0027497">nausea</symptom>.
At first I was <symptom CUI="C0027498">vomiting</symptom> a lot.
Right away I felt a sharp, shooting <symptom CUI="C0000737">pain in my upper right abdominal area </symptom>that lasted for 20-30 seconds.
I have had <symptom CUI="C0000737">abdominal pain in my upper abdomen</symptom> for the past 5-6 weeks.
I have <symptom CUI="C0014724">excessive belching</symptom>, especially after eating.
I have <symptom CUI="C0016204">flatulence</symptom>, especially in the mornings after waking.
I have <symptom CUI="C0000737">abdominal pains, slight discomfort in stomach</symptom>.
I have dizziness and <symptom CUI="C0013404">lack of breathe</symptom>.
I have very frequent <symptom CUI="C0018834">heartburn </symptom>and I seem to have gas quite often and I feel <symptom CUI="C2129199">bloated </symptom>all the time.
I woke up this morning with a migraine <symptom CUI="C0018681">headache</symptom>.
I started get very bad <symptom CUI="C0000737">abdominal pains</symptom> nearly 10 years ago.
I got a virus from my wife about 4 weeks ago and it caused me to get <symptom CUI="C3714552">very weak</symptom>, <symptom CUI="C0012833">dizzy </symptom>and <symptom CUI="C0027497">nauseous</symptom> for about a week.
I feel my <symptom CUI="C0039231">heart beating faster</symptom>.
I have very frequent <symptom CUI="C0018681">headaches</symptom>.
<symptom CUI="C2129199">Fullness in my upper abdomen</symptom> (just below the bottom of sternum)
<symptom CUI="C0014724">Unusual burping</symptom> (big burps)
<symptom CUI="C0015672">Fatigue</symptom>
I feel like there is something that's slightly <symptom CUI="C0426484">stuck in my throat</symptom>.
I have an <symptom CUI="C0037036">increase in saliva</symptom>, feel like I need to spit constantly.
My Son has been having <symptom CUI="C0000737">abdominal pains</symptom> for a while.
I'm nearly 18 and I have a <symptom CUI="C2126596">small lump on my buttock</symptom>.
I have <symptom CUI="C0000737">pain in the lower left abdomen</symptom>, right by the last rib.
I'm 21 years old and I can remember having problems with <symptom CUI="C0027497">nausea</symptom> since I was 10.
I am a 20 year old male and recently I noticed this <symptom CUI="C0000737">pain in my lower left abdomen</symptom>.
Started July 2008 with <symptom CUI="C0013428">pain whilst urinating or opening bowels</symptom>, then <symptom CUI="C0008031">chest pains</symptom>.
This past month I've been experiencing <symptom CUI="C0027497">nausea on and off</symptom>.
My daughter who just turned 16 has <symptom CUI="C0027498">bouts of morning vomiting</symptom> for the past 3-5 years.
She would <symptom CUI="C0027498">vomit early morning</symptom>, immediately upon waking.
The indigestion subsided after about two weeks however the <symptom CUI="C0000737">abdominal pain</symptom> has worsened to the point where it is causing me a great deal of discomfort.
For the past couple months, I have been experiencing all these symptoms, and they are continually worsening: <symptom CUI="C0030794">pelvic pain</symptom> in my lower right abdomen.
<symptom CUI="C0232462">Loss of appetite</symptom>
