I awoke this morning with a both <symptom CUI="C0423670">sharp and dull pain around my left shoulder</symptom>, close to the spine.
I have just began to experience severe <symptom CUI="C0231749">pains in my lower knee</symptom>.
For 2 days now I've had <symptom CUI="C0151315">stiffness in my neck</symptom>.
The <symptom CUI="C0004604">pain begins as a dull, lasting sensation throughout the upper middle of my back</symptom> but is not limited to this area.
I now have severe <symptom CUI="C0007859">chronic pain on both sides of my neck</symptom>, across the base of my skull, <symptom CUI="C0423670">along my shoulders</symptom> and <symptom CUI="C0004604">mid back</symptom>.
I have three hard <symptom CUI="C2126481">bumps on the back of my neck</symptom> in different areas.
Every morning I wake up with <symptom CUI="">back pain</symptom> so intense that I am unable to move for the first 10-15 minutes.
I have a <symptom CUI="C0024031">lower back pain</symptom> problem.
Hello I was working out about a month and a half ago and <symptom CUI="C0024031">my lower back started to accutely hurt</symptom>.
I suffer with <symptom CUI="C0004604">bad back</symptom> and <symptom CUI="C0423670">shoulder pains</symptom>.
For about a year, I experienced <symptom CUI="C0004604">back discomforts</symptom>.
Recently back from a flight ( 4 days ago ) where I had a terrible <symptom CUI="C0231710">pain on my left buttocks</symptom>.
Have had <symptom CUI="C0024031">lower back</symptom>, <symptom CUI="C0000737">abdominal</symptom> and <symptom CUI="C0039591">left testicle pain</symptom> for several months.
When I lay down to sleep I get this <symptom CUI="C0004604">stabbing sensation in the middle of my back</symptom>.
<symptom CUI="C0231710">Pain is primarily in mid buttock</symptom>.
I've been having <symptom CUI="C0024031">lower back pain</symptom> for over 2 years now.
One morning while driving I noticed a <symptom CUI="C0423670">pain in my left shoulder blade</symptom>.
I have, for the past 10 days, been experiencing <symptom CUI="C0677061">pain across my mid back</symptom>.
We went over one bump and I got a <symptom CUI="C0024031">piercing pain in my lower back</symptom>. 
I've been suffering from a pretty bad <symptom CUI="C0004604">back pain</symptom> now for 2 months.
I wake up every morning with a very <symptom CUI="C0151315">stiff neck</symptom>.
I have this <symptom CUI="C0677061">pain and tenderness in my thoracic spine</symptom> 6 months.
I have <symptom CUI="C0008031">pain in my chest</symptom> and <symptom CUI="C0423670">under shoulder blades</symptom>.
For the past 2 months i have been getting a <symptom CUI="C0024031">burning sensation pain in my lower back</symptom>.
<symptom CUI="C0007859">My neck</symptom> and <symptom CUI="C0423670">right shoulder was very painful</symptom>.
After doing a strength test evaluation again in Aug 09, I started to have <symptom CUI="C0024031">lower back pain</symptom>.
I have constant <symptom CUI="C0004604">back</symptom>, <symptom CUI="C0007859">neck</symptom> and <symptom CUI="C0231749">knee pains </symptom>and all of my joints click.
My <symptom CUI="C0004604">back gets sore and very painful</symptom>.
Sometimes when I stand up or bend over I nearly fall over from <symptom CUI="C0012833">dizziness</symptom> and the feeling blood has rushed to my head.
I first started to have <symptom CUI="C0004604">back pain</symptom> with the flu 2 months ago.
Could it be related to my <symptom CUI="C0018681">headache</symptom> and <symptom CUI="C0012833">dizziness</symptom>?
I had severe <symptom CUI="C2032349">heel pain on my left heel</symptom>.
Whenever I press my <symptom CUI="C0423670">left shoulder blade I get a kind of sharp pain</symptom>.
My <symptom CUI="C0004604">back started hurting</symptom> when I was in 6th grade.
I woke up in the middle of the night with a very <symptom CUI="C0004604">stiff and sore back</symptom>.
I've had <symptom CUI="C0004604">back pain</symptom> ranging from mild to severe for about a decade.
I have been experiencing <symptom CUI="C0024031">cronic pain along the right side of my lower back</symptom> for the past four days.
I awoke yesterday to the worst <symptom CUI="C0004604">back pain</symptom> of my entire life.
I have had stiffness and <symptom CUI="C2032437">pain in my right calf</symptom>.
I have had a <symptom CUI="C0574068">burning pain between on my right lower rib </symptom>for about 2 to 3 years.
I fell again 2 weeks ago and was experiencing extreme <symptom CUI="C0024031">lower back</symptom> and <symptom CUI="C0231749">knee pain</symptom>.
The last several days I have awakened with severe <symptom CUI="C0012833">dizziness</symptom>.
I have extreme <symptom CUI="C2127214">pain on my left leg</symptom>.
I have been having severe <symptom CUI="C0004604">back pain</symptom> that has been radiating to my right leg.
This <symptom CUI="C0004604">back pain </symptom>was fairly acute for the last 4-6 months.
I have moderate <symptom CUI="C0004604">pain in my mid back</symptom> on my left.
For the past few days I have had <symptom CUI="C0007859">neck pain</symptom> at the very base of my neck towards the left.
